PRIVACY POLICY

United Communications and its affiliates (“United”) are dedicated to providing you with a broad spectrum of servicessuch as digital TV, high-speed internet, long distance, and local service, as well as a superior customer experience. Weare committed to protecting customer privacy, and abide by the privacy rules mandated by the Federal CommunicationsCommission (FCC) and other federal and state oversight agencies. The protection of your personal information isimportant to us and we take this responsibility seriously as a key to earning and maintaining your trust.

Collection of Information – At the time that a customer like you orders or changes service, United will collect certaininformation that enables us to identify you correctly, provide you with the desired service, and bill and collect ourcharges for the services you take. This information includes, but is not limited to, your name, address, social securitynumber, employer, day time contact number, credit card or bank account numbers, credit information, and emailaddresses. If we provide local or long distance telecommunications services to you, we collect certain call and serviceinformation known as Consumer Proprietary Network Information (CPNI) which is defined separately below and which isregulated extensively by the FCC. Finally, if you use our high-speed internet or information services (such as our Internetaccess services) or visit our websites, we may collect certain information such as your IP addresses, click information,and domain, and may use “cookies” or other technologies to allow us to customize our offerings to you. By subscribingto our service and/or using our website, you agree to our collection of your personal information.

Use of your Information – United will provide any of your information to a law enforcement or national security agencyif it is requested from us by an appropriate court order, warrant, subpoena, or other lawful device.

United will also use your relevant information to provide you with the services that you have requested, communicatewith you when necessary or useful to maintain the desired quality of your services, respond to your inquiries andcomplaints, and locate and repair any problems or outages with respect to your service that come to our attention.

United is entitled to, and will, use any of your information to bill and collect for our services (including collection byagents), to investigate and resolve billing disputes, to enforce our Terms and Conditions of Service and our AcceptableUse Policy, and to prevent or fight fraud against our company, our customers and other carriers.

United may aggregate your information with that of some or all of its other customers to manage and improve ournetwork. In such cases, your information will be combined with the information of many other customers, and would beused in a manner that does not identify you.

United understands that certain personal information such as Social Security numbers, credit card numbers and bankaccount information is susceptible to identity theft. United uses that information only for service, billing and collectionpurposes, does not share it with any third parties (other than collection agents), and employs its best efforts tosafeguard it from theft.

United will use CPNI in the manner set forth separately below.

Accessing your Confidential Personal Information – If you or your Authorized User contacts us by phone, you will beasked your name and Personal Identification Number (PIN) (if PIN protected, otherwise you will be asked for otherinformation to verify your identity). In the business office, a photo id will validate a person’s identity when requestingaccount information.

Customer Propriety Network Information (CPNI) – CPNI is defined by federal statute to mean: (1) information thatrelates to the quantity, technical configuration, type, destination, location , and amount of use of a telecommunicationsservice subscribed to by any customer of a telecommunications carrier, and that is made available to the carrier by thecustomer solely by virtue of the carrier customer relationship; and (2) information contained in the bills pertaining to

telephone exchange service or telephone toll service received by a customer of a carrier. Use of CPNI is mandated byfederal law and United is required to comply.

United may use CPNI without your consent in a manner consistent with applicable law to: (1) initiate, render, bill, andcollect for our service; (2) market services among the categories of service to which you already subscribe; (3) provideinside wiring services; (4) provide maintenance, help desk, and technical support services; (5) protect our rights andenforce our Acceptable Use Policy and General Terms and Conditions; and (6) provide inbound marketing and customerservices during customer calls.

Further, after providing you with the required notice and opportunity to “opt-out”, we may use your CPNI, in a mannerconsistent with applicable law.

United takes reasonable precautions to safeguard and protect against risks of loss and unauthorized access, destruction,use, modification and disclosure of Confidential Personal Information.

Contact Us – United welcomes any questions our customers may have regarding Confidential Personal Information. It isour intent to protect our customer’s information as well as keep them well informed of the services and newtechnologies that we offer.

If you have questions about our Privacy Policy, please make them in writing to United Communications c/o ConfidentialPersonal Information, P.O. Box 38, Chapel Hill, TN 37034 or call 1-800-779-2227.

Other – United reserves the right to make changes to the Privacy Policy at any time. If we make material changes, wewill use reasonable effort to notify you via a bill message or other communication approximately 30 days prior to theeffective date of the changes. Changes to the Privacy Policy are considered effective immediately and will be posted onthe website. It is the user’s responsibility to stay current.

Last Updated – May 1, 2013
